A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Business Manager, Annual Reports, Series 4 FA809
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Business Manager, Annual Reports, Series 4
1909-1963, 1969-1970
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University
Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
FA809
9.6 Cubic Feet 8 standard record storage boxes.
Other Finding Aids
FA811 Rockefeller University records, Business Manager, Henry James Subject Files, Series 1.
FA808 Rockefeller University records, Business Manager, Correspondence, Series 2.
FA137 Rockefeller University records, Business Manager, Subject Files, Series 3.
FA810 Rockefeller University records, Business Manager, Budget Histories, Series 7.
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 210-4
Scope and Contents
Contains bursar reports, expenditures, financial summaries, monthly reports, and budgets.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement
As received.
Vivisection; Biochemistry; Cell and biomolecular sciences; Medicine, Preventive; Hospitals; Operations management; Biology -- Research; Medical technology; Medical research; Life sciences; Prevention and health; Rockefeller University; Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
- Annual reports, 1909-1963, 1969-1970; 4; 12 volumes
  Scope and Contents note
  Title varies: Report, Annual report, Financial statement, Manager's report and 1962/1963 Annual report of the Director of the Budget and Special Services.
  Made up of reports from Assistant Business Manager, Bursar, Personnel Supervisor, Librarian, Publications Office and the administrators of various auxiliary services and actions taken by the Board of Scientific Directors and the Board of Trustees.
  Includes endowments and additions to endowments; grants reports on changes in personnel and scientific staff, welfare service and Workmen's Compensation. Includes reports on improvements and. construction in buildings and grounds and new property under construction. Includes Annual reports of Press, Journals, Library, Bursar's reports of receipts, expenditures and valuations paged in separately for each year including yearly valuation schedule.
  Various charts showing growth, distribution of expenditures, increases in mailing lists of Journals and Studies. Many photographs of buildings and interiors of buildings.
  Starting 1956/1957 includes Budget authorizations and expenditures.Title varies: Report, Annual report, Financial statement, Manager's report and 1962/1963 Annual report of the Director of the Budget and Special Services.
  Starting 1956/1957 includes Budget authorizations and expenditures.
  Arrangement note
  Arranged in chronological order.
  File Plan note
  Former Classification: I 210-4
  Conditions Governing Access note
  Restricted from scholary access pending further processsing. Material 25 years old or older will be available for scholarly research once processing is completed.
  - Financial Statements, 1909-1920 (Box 1, Folder 1-15)
  - Financial Statements, 1910-1917 (Box 7, Folder 7-10)
  - Financial Statements, 1917-1921 (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
  - Financial Statements, 1919-1928 (Box 2, Folder 1-12)
  - Financial Statements, 1924-1935 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Financial Statements, 1928-1939 (Box 3, Folder 1-11)
  - Financial Statements, 1931-1939 (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
  - Financial Statements, 1939-1948 (Box 4, Folder 1-10)
  - Financial Statements, 1948-1955 (Box 5, Folder 1-14)
  - Financial Statements, 1955-1960 (Box 6, Folder 1-11)
  - Financial Statements, 1960-1963 (Box 7, Folder 1-4)
  - Financial Statements, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 5-6)